Ok, now we're going to check the brake fluid.
You locate your brake fluid and it's usually mounted up onto the firewall, in your vehicle.
Most vehicles are different but generally, it's going to be on the left hand side, in the corner, up on the firewall.
You're going to take the cap off, make sure you clean the area around the reservoir, to make sure you don't get any dirt inside of the fluid itself to contaminate the fluid.
You want to make sure you're not contaminating this fluid because it is vital to the car.
You want to read the instructions on the cap to make sure that you get the right brake fluid.
If your brake fluid gets low, then you won't have the proper braking that you need, in dyer situations.
You want to read your brake fluid to make sure you're putting the right brake fluid in.
There's different kinds, you can go from Dot one, on up to Dot five or six.
Most general cars work with Dot three or four, brake fluid.
This is a synthetic fluid, you can also get silicone fluid but it depends on what sort of vehicle you're dealing with.
You want to make sure your fluid is always at this max line, on the brake reservoir itself.
You basically just find it, take the cap off, make sure there's no debris and add fluid, if fluid is needed.
We're going to need to add fluid, in this situation.
You can generally find brake fluid at any auto parts store, at a convenient store and even the grocery store because they do have an auto fluid section, in there.
You also want to make sure that you don't spill, if you spill any, make sure you clean it off all painted surfaces because it will destroy the paint.
That sums up brake fluid, checking the brake fluid and what types of brake fluid, that you should use in your vehicle.